{
    "subject": "Donald_Knuth",
    "predicate": "isKnownFor",
    "object": "MMIX",
    "human_readable": "Donald Knuth is known for MMIX.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8802850842475891,
            "question": "What is Donald Knuth known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6189051270484924,
            "question": "Who created MMIX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761610865592957,
            "question": "What is MMIX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5428177714347839,
            "question": "Are there any other notable works by Donald Knuth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49506866931915283,
            "question": "Who might use MMIX and why?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41047385334968567,
            "question": "What are some key features of MMIX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38659462332725525,
            "question": "What field of study is Donald Knuth associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2811548411846161,
            "question": "Is there any software or hardware that uses MMIX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1747816652059555,
            "question": "What are some challenges associated with developing a system like MMIX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15339216589927673,
            "question": "How did MMIX impact the field of computer science?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Donald Knuth is known for MMIX.",
            "html": "yago_31586_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges associated with developing a system like MMIX?",
            "html": "yago_31586_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any software or hardware that uses MMIX?",
            "html": "yago_31586_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Donald Knuth associated with?",
            "html": "yago_31586_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31586_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Donald Knuth and his work on the MMIX architecture, which supports the statement that Donald Knuth is known for MMIX."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}